[Music]
we're no strangers to
love you know the rules and so do
I I full commitments while I'm thinking
of
you wouldn't get this from any other guy
I just want to tell you how I'm
feeling got to make you understand Never
Going To Give You Up never going to let
you down never going to run around and
desert you never going to make you cry
never going to say goodbye never going
to tell a lie and hurt you
we've known each other for so
long your heart's been aching but your
to sh to say it inside we both know
what's been going
on we know the game and we're going to
playing and if you ask me how I'm
feeling don't tell me you're too my you
see Never Going To Give You Up never
going to let you down never to run
around and desert you never going to
make you cry never going to say goodbye
never going to tell a lie and hurt you
never going to give you up never going
to let you down never going to run
around and desert you never going to
make you cry never going to sing goodbye
going to tell a lie and hurt
you
give
you give
you going to give going to give
you we've known each other for so
long your heart's been aching but you're
too sh to say inside we both know what's
been going
on we the game and we're going to play
it I just want to tell you how I'm
feeling got to make you understand Never
Going To Give You Up never going to let
you down never going to run around and
desert you never going to make you cry
never going to say goodbye never going
to tell you my and Hurt You Never Going
To Give You Up
never going to let you down never going
to run around and desert you never going
to make you C never going to say goodbye
never going to
tell and Hur You Never Going To Give You
Up never going to let you down never
going to run around and desert you never
going to make you going to
[Music]
goodbye
and